adultgirldirectory.com 2010-06-22

# Adult Girl Directory, escort lists, discussion, World Wide escort top 100 :: Privacy Policy

[**Adult Girl Directory.com**](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/)  is strongly committed to protecting the privacy and anonymity of our members. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers, and in particular, ensure that minors (i.e. anyone who is under the age of 18) are protected from inappropriate materials. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor and user of Adult Girl Directory.com , what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit [www.adultgirldirectory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/) , how we may use that information, whether we reveal it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct the information.  

We offer membership services only to consumers over the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect data from minors.

**Information About You**  
Upon registration for membership, **[Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/) **  will particularly ask for information about you. We, or our billing agent, will ask for your name, billing address, and credit card number in order to provide you with all of [Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/)  services.  
Because we understand your need for anonymity we generally attempt to contact you via email. Our database stores this information so that placing future orders will be quicker and easier. If you want to update your address or change credit cards, go to your  [Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/) account page and make the appropriate changes.  
We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. You can choose not to receive such information if you dont want to by letting us know on the registration screen when you sign up for our service. We may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the online medium, but you may always choose to not respond.

**Tracking Information**  
[ Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/)  will collect and store only the following nonpersonally-identifying information from you: the name of the domain name from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the Website from which you linked directly to our site. We also track your order and billing history so you can access your Account at [Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/) . This information is password-protected.  
As you browse the [Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/)  site, cookies are placed on your computers hard drive. Cookies allow us to gather information to provide you with the best service. It tells us the number and frequency of visitors to our site and its various pages. Third parties may serve some of these cookies. We analyze this data to determine which parts of our site customers like and which parts need improvement. Automatically logged information is also used to analyze trends and to administer the site.  
The only party that we may share your transaction processing information with is our credit card processor, which subsequently may share that information to a third party licensor of the fraud prevention scoring services solely for use in developing its fraud prevention modeling and for performing the fraud prevention services. All your transaction processing information provided to the Fraud Service Bureau shall be subject to written agreement between our credit card processor and the Fraud Service Bureau restricting disclosure of any Customer Data to other third parties except as necessary to perform the Fraud Services. Otherwise, all of your personal information such as name, address, email addresses and telephone number will not be shared with any third parties.

**Limited Disclosure**  
We generally do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to [Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/)  or your personal information as described above, to any third parties. We may, however, share with our actual or prospective partners aggregated statistical information about the use of [Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/)

**Security and Access**  
[ Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/)  uses a secure socket layer (SSL), which encrypts all information that is transmitted or received. This encryption process ensures that the information you give us is protected against unauthorized access.  
You can access Your Account from within the site to update and correct your name, email address, password, postal address, credit cards, mailing list preferences, and services requested.  
We have implemented technology and security features, as well as strict internal guidelines, to safeguard the privacy of your personal information from unauthorized access or improper use. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. While we make every effort to ensure that your information is secure on our system, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. 

**[Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/)  Privacy Policy Changes**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy for [Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/)  , we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Such changes are at the discretion of [Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/) , and are done with privacy, anonymity and safety in mind. 

**Your Acceptance Of These Terms**  
By using this site, you hereby agree to [Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/) Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this policy, please do not use our site. If you do continue to visit [Adult Girl Directory.com](http://www.adultgirldirectory.com/) , we will assume that you have agreed to the conditions and terms under which we operate.

If you have any questions, please feel free to [contact us ](mailto:info@adultgirldirectory.com)
